

ABOUT ME

Programming passionate since one year. Spending most of my free time learning HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. Currently seeking my first job in the industry. By education, I am a logistics engineer with experience working in both domestic and international warehouses, in both executive and positions. management Additionally, I have the experience in the gastronomy, journalism, and transport industries.

SKILLS

html, css, javaScript, react.js Intermediate

Microsoft Office

Intermediate

Basic

English language

B2 - Intermediate

Prawo jazdy

category - B

Forklifts operation

UDT qualifications

HOBBIES

Football

Music

Writing lyrics

Graphic

Hiking

Climbling

Traveling

Norbert Sarapata

Front-end developer / Logistics engineer

C Phone number: +48 664 447 122 **E-mail:** sarapata.norbert@gmail.com

■ Website: norfeone-design.pl **Birth-date:** 24.08.1994

Place of living: Cracow

Job experience

Jumbo Distribution Center

Nieuwegein, Netherlands 2023-2024

Clearing Station Operator, Captain

Production work in a modern, partially automated warehouse in the Netherlands. Managing and supervising the work of an international team. Transfering and executioning of Process Leader's commands. Advising and cooperation with Process Leader. Independent decision making and reacting to dynamic situations. Working in all warehouse departments (in two as a captain).

Leroy Merlin

Cracow 2022

Logistics Manager

Organizing work of warehouse employers. Providing optimal and safe flowless of goods between suplier and customer. Providing professional service of customers orders. Taking care of stack level and warehouse processes..

Uber, Bolt, Freenow

Cracow 2022

Driver

Transportation of clients of popular mobile applications.

Jumbo Distribution Center

Nieuwegein, Netherlands 2020-2021

Pizzer-man, driver

Making and delivering pizza.

Clearing Station Operator, Captain

Fabryka Pizzy Cracow

Delikatesy Extra

2018-2020

Cracow 2017-2018

Warehouse logistics

Keeping the warehouse in order. Supervising over the proper storage of resources. Placing and accepting orders. Customer service in the store hall. Arranging and fronting products on store shelves.

Education

MMC School 2023-...

html, css, javaScript, react.js

Learning programming languages with the help of certified courses led by Mateusz Maj.

University of Economics Cracow

2016-2020

International logistics

Completed engineering studies.

VII High School Cracow

2010-2013

Mathematics and physic

"I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation)."